{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "I'm sorry, but you ___ sit there. That table's reserved.\n",
            "a": "couldn't",
            "b": "wouldn't",
            "c": "can't",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sue used to ___ speak Arabic fluently, but she's forgotten a lot of it now.\n",
            "a": "be able to",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "can",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The coach promised that Paul ___ play in the next match, so Paul was delighted.\n",
            "a": "would",
            "b": "must",
            "c": "can",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm glad Helen didn't ask me for advice about her boyfriend. I ___ what to say.\n",
            "a": "couldn't have known",
            "b": "wouldn't have known",
            "c": "can't have known",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "John knew there was something wrong with his car but he ___ take it to the garage. He couldn't afford to pay for any repairs.\n",
            "a": "mustn't",
            "b": "won't",
            "c": "wouldn't",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think you ___ eat those wild mushrooms. They could be poisonous.\n",
            "a": "should",
            "b": "must",
            "c": "might",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought a jacket for £60 last month, and now the same jacket is in the sale for £30! I ___ for the sale.\n",
            "a": "should wait",
            "b": "should have waited",
            "c": "should have been waiting",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you need a car to collect your furniture, I ___ lend you mine.\n",
            "a": "was able to",
            "b": "managed to",
            "c": "can",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lucy fell off a ladder while she was painting her flat. She broke her leg but luckily she ___ get to the phone and call an ambulance.\n",
            "a": "could",
            "b": "was able to",
            "c": "should",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark ___ bring a map with him. I don't know how to get to Dan's house.\n",
            "a": "would",
            "b": "had better",
            "c": "had better to",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "25",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}